Any human whose name is written in this notebook shall... die.
このノートに名前を書かれた人間は…
死ぬ!?
Please! Stop!!
お願い…やめて
Okay then, let's see what happens.
さあ…どうなる？
don't read this line
Okay then, let's see what happens.
The Death Note... It's the real deal!
デスノートは…本物だ!!
Don't assume that a human who has used the Death Note can go to Heaven or Hell.
デスノートを使った人間が…
天国や地獄にいけると思うな
I'm going to let the world know of my existence.
世の中に知らしめるんだ…
僕の存在を…
That there is someone who can, and will, pass righteous judgement!
正義の裁きを下す者がいるって事を！
And then, I'll become... the God of my new world!
そして僕も…
新世界の神となる！
And then, I'll become... the God of my new world!
Showdown
He was over-flooded with satisfaction and zealous, then finally his dream came true.
He was overflow then with satisfaction…
I could never tell what he was thinking, so I had to finish with him
何考えてたのが全然わかんないから、もう見切った
マジで？
Seriously? So, after that, what happened with your dad?
ってあの後のオヤジと、あれからどうだった？
Yagami-kun? Could you please translate the previous passage into Japanese?
では…夜神くん
内緒
Yagami-kun? Could you please translate the previous passage into Japanese?
今の文章、和訳してください
Yes.
はい
Having finally made his dream a reality, he was overwhelmed by the sense of his own achievement and the joy it brought him.
ついに夢を現実のものとした彼は、
その夢の完全なる成就と、
それによる至福の喜びに浸っている
よくできました
Well done. A perfect translation, but I'd expect nothing less from you, Yagami-kun.
さすがは夜神くん
完璧な回答ですね
We'll leave it here for today.
それじゃ、今日はここまでにします
Man, am I glad that that's finally over. This "school" thing really bores me.
やっと終りか
退屈だな、学校って所も
Hey, Light.
おい、ライト
Light, are you listening to me?
ライト、聞いてるのか
Don't talk to me. Other people can hear my voice, unlike yours.
話しかけるな
僕の声はリュークと違って、他の人にも聞こえるんだ
Don't talk to me. Other people can hear my voice, unlike yours.
ふん、つまんねぇの
Boring.
Hey, Light! We're all gonna head to th--
おい、月、
これから、俺たち…
Sorry. I've got things to do.
悪い、用があるんだ
You don't have "things" to do.
用なんてないだろう、
Aren't you just gonna go home like always?
いつもどおりまっすぐ家に帰るだけじゃないのか？
What are you talking about? I do have "things" to do.
何を言ってるんだ、用はあるよ
Very important things...
そう、とっても大事な用事がね…
Yamada is suspected of stabbing a fellow employee in the stomach at a restaurant in Kabukichi, Shinjuku, yesterday.
山田容疑者は、昨日新宿区歌舞伎町の飲食店で、
店にあった刃渡りおよそ12cmのナイフを使い、
The knife was from the restaurant, and was roughly twelve inches long.
後輩従業員の下腹部を刺した疑いを持たれています
山田容疑者は…
Hey... Hey, Light?
おい
おい、ライト
Hey... Hey, Light?
What?
なんだ
What's with all the effort?
随分一生懸命だな
It's because I can't afford to waste any time.
時間を無駄にできないからね
The time that I have to write names in the notebook is limited from when I come home and until I go to bed.
ノートに名前を書ける時間は限られている、
学校から帰ってきて寝るまでくらいだ、
It's important that I maintain my grades, so I can't sleep in class.
成績も今までどおりトップでいることも大切だ
授業中に居眠りもできないし、
I can't neglect my studies at home or cram school either.
家や塾での勉強もしっかりやっておかないとね
Besides, losing sleep will affect my health and my mental capacity.
そして睡眠不足も敵だ、
健康や思考能力を損なう
If I'm serious about changing the world into a purer place, no matter how much time I have, it will never be enough.
なにしろ、世の中を悪のない理想の世界に変えるんだ
時間はいくらあっても足りない…
Huh? Onii-chan, why is your door locked?
あれ、お兄ちゃん何で鍵なんか閉めてんの？
..It's Sayu.
粧裕か…
What is it?
なに？
Can you help me with my homework?
宿題教えて
Oh.. Yeah, okay.
ああ…いいよ
Right now, in Maths, we're doing quadratic equations.
数学の二次函数で～す
Sorry to disturb you when you're studying, but I just don't get it.
勉強してるとこごめんね、
でももう、ちんぷんかんぷんなの
お願いしま～す
Thanks!
Yes, yes.
はいはい…
Watch out, Light. If anyone touches that notebook in your drawer, they'll be able to see me.
気をつけろよ、ライト
今引き出しの中のノートに触った人間には、
Watch out, Light. If anyone touches that notebook in your drawer, they'll be able to see me.
オレの姿が見える
You waited until now to mention such an important detail?
そういう大切な事を今頃、
Damned Shinigami..
この死神は…
What's wrong, Onii-chan?
どうしたの、お兄ちゃん？
…あ、いや
Nothing. Anyway, which bit are you stuck on?
それで？一体何が解らないんだ？
Umm.. All of it?
うんっとね…全部かな
ICPO, or Interpol, stands for International Criminal Police Organization
( ICPO =国際刑事警察機構会議)
There have been 52 known cases in this week alone.
この一週間で分っているだけで52人、
All of them involved heart attacks.
その全てが心臓麻痺だ
All of them involved criminals that are either already in jail, or being pursued by the police.
全て手配中の、もしくは刑務所に留置されていた犯罪者たちです
I think it's safe to assume that there are still many other deaths that we are yet unaware of.
死んだことが確認されていない犯罪者たちもいるでしょうな
そうなると軽く百人以上か？
In which case, the total could easily be over 100.
It's already started, Chief.
もう始まってますよ、局長
Sorry, I had to take a call from headquarters.
あぁ、ちょっと本部から連絡がな…
※(「がな」、があるなの略)
But they're all criminals who should have faced the death penalty sooner or later.
しかしいずれも、死刑になっても仕方のない犯罪者ばかりだ、
Why should we care?
別に構わないのでは…
Idiot!
馬鹿な！大犯罪者だろうと死刑囚だろうと､殺せば殺人です
It doesn't matter whether it's a criminal, death row prisoner or whatever! If you kill someone, then that's murder!
But surely it hasn't been confirmed as a homicide yet, has it?
殺人と決まった訳ではないでしょう
Over 100 criminals dying of heart attacks, coincidences like that doesn't exist! It's obviously murder!
百人以上が心臓麻痺なんて偶然があるか？
殺人に決まってる！
Over 100 criminals dying of heart attacks, coincidences like that doesn't exist! It's obviously murder!
Do you honestly think it's possible to commit so many murders, in different locations, almost all at the same time?
そんな広範囲で同時と言ってもいい殺人が…可能ですかねぇ
We're treating this as an elaborate assassination plot that is being carried out by a large organization.
我々は、大組織による緻密な計画殺人と見ています
A large organization? Then, surely the FBI or the CIA must be involved!
そんな大組織などと言ったら、
FBI か CIA が絡んでいるとしか思えませんな
もう一度言ってみたまえ！
What did you say?!
Whoa, whoa. Let's not mess around here.
まぁまぁ、冗談は慎んで下さい
The first thing we need to determine, is whether this is murder or just a coincidence.
まずはこれが殺人なのか偶然なのか、その解明でしょう
But, the coroners have all ruled a verdict of "heart attack with no known cause".
しかし検死の報告では、みんな原因の分らない心臓麻痺でしょ？
Opening a police investigation into heart attacks is going to get us nowhere.
心臓麻痺って死因から洗ったのでは、何も出ませんからね
Jeez, if only they'd use a knife or something, then we'd have something to investigate.
まったくだ、ナイフでも刺さっていれば、洗いようもあるが…
Then it looks like we've got no choice but to bring in "L" again!
こうなったらまた「 L 」に解決してもらうしかありませんな
Chief, what's "L"?
局長…なんです？「 L 」って
Ah, I'd forgotten that it's your first time here at this conference.
あぁ…君はこの会議初めてだったな…
"L" is someone whose real name and whereabouts are unknown. We don't even know what he looks like.
「 L 」と言うのは、
名前も、居場所も、顔すら誰も知らない
Yet, he always manages to solve every single case he takes on.
しかし、どんな難事件でも必ず解決してしまう、
He's solved countless mysterious incidents all over the world.
世界の迷宮入り事件の数々を解いてきた、この世界の影のトップ
He's the best of those hidden deep within the shadows.. Our trump card. That sums him up.
最後の切り札…そんなところだ
But I've heard that L is supposedly an extremely arrogant individual who'll only take on cases that interests him personally.
しかし「 L 」は、
自分が興味を持った事件にしか動かない、
傲慢な人物というじゃないか
その通りだ、
Exactly! We don't even have a way of contacting him!
それに、我々からはコンタクトも取れない
L is already on the move.
L はもう動いています
L has already begun his investigations into these incidents.
L は既に、この事件の捜査を始めています
Wa-Watari.
ワ…『ワタリ』
Huh? Watari?
えっ？『ワタリ』
He's the one man who knows how to contact L.
L とコンタクトを取れる唯一の男だ、
Nobody knows his true identity either.
もっともワタリの正体も誰も知らない
Everyone, quiet please. L will now speak.
お静かに願います、
L の声を今、お聞かせします
Greetings to all of you at the ICPO.
ICPO の皆様…
I am L.
L です
What's with the secrecy? What're you planning to do in this isolated place, Light?
こんな人気のない所で…
何をこそこそしてるんだ、ライト
デスノートに触った人間には、リュークの姿が見えるんだろ？
Anyone who touches the Death Note can see you, right?
I can't risk keeping such a dangerous article in a regular place.
こんな危険な物、普通に持ってなんていられない
Up until now, I'd been thinking that even if by chance this notebook was seen by my family,
今までは、仮にノートを家族に見られても、
I could end the matter by saying I was "taking records of incidents to study for when I become a detective".
「刑事になる為の勉強として事件の記録を取っていた」
で済むくらいに思っていたけど…
Right now, I'm walking a really thin line.
僕はギリギリの綱渡りをしているんだ、
Just one mistake.. and I might have to kill off one of my own family.
下手を打てば僕は、自分の家族を…
殺すことになってしまう
The difficulty of this case is on a scale that I've never experienced before.. and, it's an atrocious murder case that I will never forgive!
この事件は…かつてない規模で難しい、
そして、絶対に許してはならない、凶悪の殺人事件です
The difficulty of this case is on a scale that I've never experienced before.. and, it's an atrocious murder case that I will never forgive!
In order to solve this case, I would like to have everyone in the ICPO,
この事件を解決する為に、是非 ICPO の皆様が…
no, the organizations you all represent throughout the world, make the decision to lend their full support to me in this meeting.
いや、全世界のあらゆる機関が、
私に全面協力してくださる事をこの会議で決議して頂きたい
In addition, I will require special cooperation from the Japanese police force.
そして、特に日本警察の協力を強く要請します
W-Why Japan?!
な、何故日本だった？
Whether there's one or more culprits involved, the probability of them being Japanese is extremely high.
犯人は複数であれ単独であれ、
日本人である可能性が極めて高い
Even if they're not Japanese, it's likely that they are in Japan.
日本人ではないにせよ、日本に潜伏している
What are you basing this theory on?!
何を根拠に
Why Japan?
何故日本なのか…
I hope to be able to show you soon.. when I go head-to-head with the culprit.
それは近々犯人との直接対決でお見せできると思います
Head-to-head?
直接対決？
とにかく、捜査本部は日本において頂きたい
In any case, I'd like the investigation headquarters to be based in Japan.
That was easier than I thought.
割と簡単にできたな…
ん？ノートを隠せたって事か
You mean you've managed to hide the notebook?
Yeah.. in this drawer.
ああ、この引き出しの中にね
Doesn't seem to be particularly hidden.
それで隠した事になるのか？
Isn't that key a bit of a give-away?
鍵つけっぱなしだぞ
That's the whole point.
それでいいんだ、
It's better that it is noticeable.
むしろ、鍵はわざと目立つ所に置いたほうがいい
ただの日記帳じゃないか
Isn't that just a normal diary?
I'm guessing that most people will have their curiosity satisfied by finding this inside.
多分殆どの人間は、
この単なる日記帳を読むことで、
この引き出しの秘密に満足する
But the real key.. is this.
でも、本当の鍵は…
こっち
僕の机の周辺でのどこに転がっていても不思議じゃない、
Just an everyday item you'd expect to find on any desk.. The center of a ball-point pen.
ただのボールペンだ、その芯を使う
それが鍵なのか？
And that's the key?
Yes. On closer examination, you'll find a small hole in the bottom.
そう、引き出しの裏に、
よく見ないと分らない小さな穴がある
The pen's center is inserted into the hole.
その穴にこれを入れるんだ…
I see. A fake base, huh?
なるほど、二重底か…
That, combined with the diary, means that it'll probably be safe.
まぁ日記のフェイクもあるし、それなら見つからないだろう
It's not just that.
それだけじゃない
ん？
Even if someone does figure out that there's a fake base, there's no way they could get their hands on this notebook.
たとえ二重底だとわかったとしても…
こうしてノートを手に取る事は、まずできない
You see, this ball-point pen acts as an insulator preventing the flow of electricity round this circuit.
わかる？
この電気を通さないボールペンの芯が絶縁体となり、
電流を塞き止めている
As the fake base is returned, the rubber stops the flow of electricity.
中底を閉めた時には、
このゴムが絶縁体となり、電流は流れない
However, if someone tries to force the fake base open, the circuit will connect and the gasoline in this thin plastic bag will instantly incinerate the notebook.
しかし、もし誰かが強引に中底をはずせば…
その瞬間、薄いビニールに入ったガソリンに火が付き…
ノートは一気に燃え上がる
All the evidence will be destroyed.
完全に証拠は湮滅される…という仕掛けだ
If I am asked about this I'll just tell them, "I didn't want anyone to read my diary."
燃やした理由は、
「本当の日記を隠していて、見られたくなかったから」と言う、
It's a believable excuse. After all, it's human nature to hide your own diary.
一番人間らしい理由でまぁ通る
物がノートだしね
I've heard that the main problem humans have with a Death Note is how to hide it.
デスノートを人間が持った時、
その隠し場所に一番困るという話は聞いていたが…
Light, you're probably the first person to have given it this much thought.
ここまでやったのもライト、多分お前が初めてだ
Though that is a pretty risky setup.
それにしても、危険な細工だな
One mistake and you could end up in flames.
少し手順を間違えただけで、自分が大火傷するぞ
Risk? Sometimes you say some funny things, Ryuk.
危険？また変な事を言うねリューク
This whole thing has been a risk from the start...
僕は最初から危険を犯しているじゃないか、
From the minute I found the Death Note.
デスノートを手にした時点でね
Compared to that, this doesn't even qualify as a risk.
それに比べたら、こんな者は危険のうちに入らない
On the contrary, it actually protects me.
むしろ逆に僕を安全にするんだ
I mean, a death sentence? Or a small house fire? Which do you think is better?
家から小火が出るのと死刑になるのは、
どっちがいいか、さ
Last night in a prison in western Tokyo, Kurotsukayama Naoki, aged 32, previously convicted for armed robbery, has been reported to have died of a sudden heart attack.
昨夜、東京都西刑務所の所内で、
凶悪強盗犯として収容されていた、黑塚山尚紀受刑者32歳が
突然、心臓麻痺で死亡しました
This sudden phenomenon of inmates dying from heart attacks appears to be continuing..
立続けに受刑者が心臓麻痺で亡くなるという、
異例の事態を受け…
Man, this is incredible! Criminals are dropping like flies!
すごいよな、悪人がバンバンしびてんじゃん
It's kinda scary, but at the same time, it's exhilarating!
ちょっと恐いけど、ある意味爽快だよね
I guess this means that we can't risk doing anything bad.
でもこうなると悪い事できないね…
So, you reckon the police are probably behind this?
やっぱ…警察がやってんのかな？
The police don't have that kind of power! Don't you know who it is?
警察にそんな力ないって
お前知らないの？
The police don't have that kind of power! Don't you know who it is?
Eh? What?!
えっ、なんだい？
It's "Kira" who's behind this. "Kira".
キラだよ、キラ
Wonder who'll be next?
次は誰が殺されるのかな…
"Kira, kill them all."
Check this out, Ryuk.
見てみろよ、リューク
ん？
Websites like this have already started to emerge.
もうこんなホームページまでできているんだ
救世主キラ伝説…
"The legend of Kira - Our saviour"
カッコイイじゃないか、
Pretty cool.
This about you?
これお前のことか？
Yeah.
ああ、殺し屋と言う意味の「 Killer 」から来ているらしい
Kira taken from the english word "Killer".
Can't really say that I appreciate that too much, but I guess that's what the world now knows me as.
それは少し気に入らないが、
僕はもう世界的に、このキラになっている
Can't really say that I appreciate that too much, but I guess that's what the world now knows me as.
I can get so many sites like this just from a mere search on the word "kira".
キラと検索するだけですでに、この手のページがごまんとあるんだ
In the papers and on TV, it's still not been reported as anything but "a succession of strange deaths amongst the criminals".
まだ新聞やテレビでは、
「凶悪犯罪者の相次ぐ変死」くらいにしか、公表されていない…
But, the people of this world are already starting to become aware that there's someone out there judging them, in the name of justice.
しかし、世界中の人間がもう感じているんだ
正義の裁きをする者の存在を…
ほう？
Humans are like that, Ryuk.
人間って言うのはそんな生き物なんだ、リューク
あっ？
例えば、学校のホームルームで、
This is unlikely, but if anyone asked if killing bad people was wrong in school, people would get on their moral high horse, saying "That's wrong!".
「悪い人間を殺していいか」なんて議題が、あがるわけがない
しかし、もしそれが議題となったらみんなが良い子ぶり…
This is unlikely, but if anyone asked if killing bad people was wrong in school, people would get on their moral high horse, saying "That's wrong!".
『それはいけない事です』
Of course, that is the correct answer to give.
って言うに決まっている
勿論、そう答えるのが正しいし、
人間は、公共の場などでは、表面上そうでなくてはならない
Humans will always seek to maintain appearances in public.
But this is what they're really thinking.
しかし本音はこっちだ
恐いのか、表だって僕の存在を認めようとはしないけれど、
Even if they're too scared to support me publicly, they can hide behind the anonymity of the Internet.
誰が書いたも分らないインターネット上ではもう…
KIRA
Support for "Kira" is growing.
『キラ』が蔓延している
They don't have to say it, because they already know, someone is erasing the wicked.
口に出さないだけで、もうみんな分っているんだ
悪い奴が誰かに消されていると…
The innocent are screaming inside; "Go for it Kira!", while those who are guilty, run and hide in fear.
そして、自分に非のない者が、心の中で「キラ頑張れ」と叫び、
非のある者は、自分に天罰が下る事に怯える…
This is how it should be.
これでいいんだ、
It truly is progressing exactly as I'd planned.
まさに計画通りに事は進んでいる…
Notice
The scheduled program
will be interrupted
for a special broadcast.
え…番組の途中ですが、
Apologies for the interruption, but we now bring you a live worldwide broadcast from the ICPO, Interpol.
ICPO 、インターポールからの全世界同時特別生中継を行います
お？なんだ？
Huh? What's this?
インターポール？
Interpol?
It looks like they're ready to begin.
それでは始めます
I am the only person who can control the entire world's police forces, Lind L. Tailor.
私は全世界の警察を動かせる唯一の人間
LIND . L . TAILOR
I go by the code name.. "L".
通称…「 L 」です
な…なんだこいつ？
Who the hell?
And so it begins..
ついに始まったな…
しかし、今まで顔出さなかったんですよね
But I don't understand. He's never shown his face before.
Why now?
どうして今になって…
I guess it means he's taking this seriously.
L も本気って事だろう
So, L... We've followed every single one of your orders, now it's time for you to fulfill those promises you made at the ICPO conference.
さあ L 、こっちは言われた通りにやってるんだ
ICPO 会議で言った事を証明してもらおう
This successive murdering of criminals is unforgivable, and must not go unpunished.
あいつが犯罪者を狙った連続殺人…
これは絶対に許してはならない、史上最大の凶悪犯罪です
This successive murdering of criminals is unforgivable, and must not go unpunished.
I guarantee I will find and catch the ring leader, or "Kira".
よって私はこの犯罪の首謀者…
俗に謂われる「キラ」、必ず捕まえる
He says he'll guarantee that he'll catch you.
「必ず捕まえる」ってよ
ふん、馬鹿め…
Fool! There's no way he can catch me.
捕まるわけがない
It's a Death Note!
デスノートなんだよ！
As long as they don't find it, what proof will they have?!
このノートをおさえない限り、証拠なんて何も残らないんだ
Catching me is impossible! Absolutely impossible!!
捕まえるなんて…絶対不可能だ
I'd already anticipated that the police would get involved.
警察が動くのも、こんなのが出てくるのも計画のうちさ…
Kira, I can guess what your motivation might be, but what you're doing is evil!
キラ、お前がどのような考えで、このような事をしているのか、
大体想像はつく
Kira, I can guess what your motivation might be, but what you're doing is evil!
しかし、お前のしている事は…悪だ！
I'm the evil one...?
僕が…悪だと…
僕は正義だ！
I am justice!!
I save the weak from evil and will become the God of a world that everyone desires!
悪に怯える弱い者を救い…
誰もが理想とする新世界の…
神となる男だ！
Those who try to cross God are the true evil ones!
そしてその神に逆らう者…
それこそが悪だ！
I can't believe that you're this stupid, L.
間抜けすぎるぜ、 L
もう少し賢ければ、面白くなったかもしれないのに…
This could have been fun, if you'd been a little smarter.
僕に逆らうと、どうなるか…
I'll show the world what happens when you cross me, L.
世界中が注目しているよ
L…
Five seconds... Four.. Three.. Two.. One..
あと五秒…
四…
Five seconds... Four.. Three.. Two.. One..
三…
二…
Five seconds... Four.. Three.. Two.. One..
一…
What's the matter? Now, what do you have to say?!
どうした、なんとか言ってみろ
I can't believe it...
信じられない…
I tested it just in case, but I never thought it could actually be true..
もしやと思って試してみたが…
まさかこんな事が…
Kira, it seems you can kill people without having to be there in person.
キラ、お前は直接手を下さずに人を殺せるのか、
I wouldn't have been able to believe this if I hadn't just witnessed it.
この目で見るまではとても信じられなかった…
Listen closely, Kira; if you did indeed kill the "Lind L. Tailor" on screen, I can tell you that he was in fact a criminal that was due to be put to death today.
よく聞け、キラ
もしお前がテレビに映っていた、
LIND . L . TAILOR を殺したのなら…
Listen closely, Kira; if you did indeed kill the "Lind L. Tailor" on screen, I can tell you that he was in fact a criminal that was due to be put to death today.
それは今日この時間に死刑になる予定だった男だ、
That was not me.
私ではない
What?
なに？
You wouldn't have heard of him on the news or through the Internet. He was a criminal that was captured by the police in absolute secrecy.
テレビやネットでは報道されていない、
警察が極秘に捕まえた犯罪者だ…
Looks like not even you have information on these kinds of killers.
さすがのお前も、この犯罪者の情報は手に入れてないようだな
He definitely got ya this time.
やられたな
But as for L, he certainly does exist, as my own persona.
だが L という私は実在する
Now, try and kill me!!
さぁ、私を殺してみろ
Y-You bastard...
コ、コイツ…
Go on then!
さあどうした？
What the hell's going on?!
なんだこれは
早くやってみろ
Hurry up!
すごい事になってるぞ
Come on, hurry up!
さあ早く、殺してみろ
死ぬ気か、 L
Are you trying to kill yourself, L?!
What's wrong?
What's going on?
なにこれ？
He's taunting Kira.
どうした、できないかよ
キラ対 L だってよ
今ここにいるんだ
Go on! Kill me!
途中中継だぜ…
さあ来いキラ、私を殺してみろ
Come on!
え、なに、こわい…
What? This is scary!
Kill me!
Awesome!
すげぇ
It's L vs. Kira!
やれ、キラ
どうした、できないのか？
What's the matter? Can't you do it?
So, it seems you can't kill me.
どうやら、私は殺せないようだな
So, there are certain people you can't kill.
殺せない人間もいる…
That's a nice hint.
いいヒントをもらった
お返してといっては何だが、
As a reward, I'll tell you one more thing.
もうひとついいことを教えてやろう
We lied about this being a live worldwide broadcast.
この中継は、全世界同時中継と銘打ったが、
実は日本の関東地区にしか放送されていない
This announcement is currently only being broadcast across the Kanto region of Japan.
な…
時間差で各地区に流す予定だったが、もうその必要も無くなった
We were planning to broadcast it at different times, across different regions, but it seems that there is no longer any need for this.
I know you're in Kanto.
お前は…今関東にいる
Hey, this guy, L, is pretty good.
やるな、 L の奴
Your first killing was overlooked by the police as it was such a small incident.
小さな事件で警察は見逃していたが、
However, your first victim was in fact the phantom killer in Shinjuku.
この一連の事件の最初の犠牲者は新宿の通り魔だ
While the other high profile criminals were dying of heart attacks,
大犯罪者が心臓麻痺で死んでいく中、
この通り魔の罪は目立って軽い
this was the one incident that stuck out as being quite a heavy punishment for a relatively low profile crime.
In addition, that incident was only reported within Japan.
しかも、この事件は日本でしか報道されていなかった
Otoharada Kurou
Just those pieces of information were enough for me to figure it out.
これだけで十分推理できた
お前が日本にいる事、
It means that you are in Japan, and that that criminal was your first "experiment".
そしてこの犠牲者第一号は…
お前の殺しのモルモットだったという事だ
Due to its large population, this announcement was first broadcast in the Kanto region.
人口の集中する関東に最初に中継し、
And what luck! We found you.
そこにお前が居たのはラッキーだった
To be honest, I never thought it would go this smoothly.
ここまで自分の思惑通りいくとは正直思っていなかったが…
キラ、お前を死刑台に送るのもそう遠くないかもしれない…
Kira, it seems like it won't be too long before I can sentence you to death.
やっぱり、さすがですね、 L って…
Looks like L's lived up to his reputation.
Yes, he's been able to prove Kira's existence, the nature of his crime, and that he's somewhere in Japan.
ん…キラの存在、殺人…
そして日本に居る事までも証明した…
キラ、
Kira, I'm curious to know your true motives behind this, but I guess that can wait until I've caught you.
お前がどんな手段で殺人を行っているのかとても興味がある
しかしそんな事は…
お前を捕まえれば分ることだ
ではまた会おう、キラ…
Let's meet again soon, Kira.
He... thinks he's going to sentence me to death?
僕を…
死刑台に送るだと…
Interesting!
面白い…
受けてたとうじゃないか…
I'll take you on.
So, both of you are trying to find someone whose name you don't know, and whose face you won't recognize.
お互いに顔も名前も全てが分らない相手を見つけ出す…
And the first one to be found dies...
そして…見つかったほうが死ぬ
おもしれ
やっぱり人間って…面白！
I knew it. Humans are.. so much fun!!
L..
L …
Kira..
キラ…
I'll hunt you down, and kill you!
必ずお前お探し出して…
必ずお前を探し出して…
I'll hunt you down, and kill you!
始末する！
I'm..
僕が…
私が…
JUSTICE!
正義だ！
To be continued
L を探し出すのは僕じゃない、
警察が L を突き止める…
そして僕が… L を消す
また少し、リュークを楽しませてあげられるかもね